<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>


    <string name="Q1"> "I love you very much, probably more than anybody could love another person." – 50 First Dates </string>
    <string name="Q2"> “Love is that condition in which the happiness of another person is essential to your own.” – Robert A. Heinlein </string>
    <string name="Q3"> “To love is to burn, to be on fire.” – Jane Austen </string>
    <string name="Q4"> “In the end we discover that to love and let go can be the same thing.” – Jack Kornfield </string>
    <string name="Q5"> “Pleasure of love lasts but a moment. Pain of love lasts a lifetime.” – Bette Davis </string>
    <string name="Q6"> “Love is so short, forgetting is so long.” – Pablo Neruda </string>
    <string name="Q7"> “Love is a thing that is full of cares and fears.” – Ovid </string>
    <string name="Q8"> “Love is not love until love’s vulnerable.” – Theodore Roethke </string>
    <string name="Q9"> “All our dreams can come true, if we have the courage to pursue them.” —Walt Disney </string>
    <string name="Q10"> “If people are doubting how far you can go, go so far that you can’t hear them anymore.” —Michele Ruiz </string>
    <string name="Q11"> “I wake up every morning and think to myself, ‘How far can I push this company in the next 24 hours.’” —Leah Busque </string>
    <string name="Q12"> “It’s hard to beat a person who never gives up.” —Babe Ruth </string>
    <string name="Q13"> “The best time to plant a tree was 20 years ago. The second best time is now.” ―Chinese Proverb </string>
    <string name="Q14"> “Everything you can imagine is real.”―Pablo Picasso </string>
    <string name="Q15"> “Whatever you are, be a good one.” ―Abraham Lincoln </string>
    <string name="Q16"> “Happiness is not something ready made. It comes from your own actions.” ―Dalai Lama XIV </string>
    <string name="Q17"> “Do what you feel in your heart to be right―for you’ll be criticized anyway.” ―Eleanor Roosevelt </string>
    <string name="Q18"> “It’s no use going back to yesterday, because I was a different person then.” ―Lewis Carroll </string>
    <string name="Q19"> “Do one thing every day that scares you.” ―Eleanor Roosevelt </string>
    <string name="Q20"> “Impossible is just an opinion.” —Paulo Coelho </string>

</resources>
